<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Trusted Tiny Things</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_nfc">NFCActivity</string>
    <string name="accept">Accept </string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="scan">Please place your device close to the <b>NFC tag</b></string>
    <string name="terms_conditions"><b>Trusted Tiny Things</b> is a research addressing some of the challenges inherent in developing the vision of the Internet of Things (IoT) as a dynamic global network of sensors and the like, based on standard and interoperable communication protocols. 
We will make use of the data generated by users only to support the academic research of Trusted Tiny Things. <p>Selected elements of this research project may be subject to additional approval; we will seek consent from associated participants as appropriate. 
Data collected by the Trusted Tiny Things Software Platform is stored securely and password protected; our servers are located in a secure environment and server administration is handled only by members of University of Aberdeen staff working on the Trusted Tiny Things project. We strongly recommend that you keep alternative copies of your data as we will not be liable for loss or damage to data while it is stored within our systems. 
The Trusted Tiny Things Software Platform must not be used for any commercial purpose whatsoever or for any illegal or unauthorised purpose. When you use the Trusted Tiny Things Software Platform you must comply with all applicable UK laws relating to online conduct (including, without limitation, content which can be posted online) and with any applicable international laws, including the local laws in your country of residence.		</p><p>Anyone can become a registered member simply by completing the registration process and agreeing to these terms and conditions.				
You may remove your profile and content at any time however it is important to be aware that we may be unable to delete certain elements related to uploaded content, for example commentary relating to a device cannot be removed but will instead be anonymised.  				</p><p>This service complies with the University of Aberdeen - Policy on Data Protection (http://www.abdn.ac.uk/staffnet/documents/policy-zone-governance-and-compliance/DPApolicy.pdf) and is governed by the University of Aberdeen - Conditions for using IT Facilities (http://www.abdn.ac.uk/staffnet/documents/policy-zone-information-policies/DIT_cond-IT.pdf).</p><p><b>Note:</b> Please contact e.pignotti@abdn.ac.uk if you wish to use the Trusted Tiny Things Software Platform but do not wish to be included in our research.</p></string>
    <string name="title_activity_capability">CapabilityActivity</string>

</resources>
